Guide to the Donald Oliver/Chelsea Music Archive, 1907-2008 (bulk 1962-1991) MSS.254
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series I: Librettos and Playbills
  - Oh Boy!, [1917] (Box 13, Folder 15)
    Book and Lyrics by Guy Bolton Music by Jerome Kern
  - Oh, Brother: An Original Musical Comedy, [1981] (Box 13, Folder 16)
    Book and Lyrics by Donald Driver Music by Michael Valenti
  - Oh Captain!, [1958] (Box 13, Folder 17)
    Book by Al Morgan and Jose Ferrer Music and Lyrics by Jay Livingston and Ray Evans
  - Oh, Kay!, undated (Box 13, Folder 18)
    Book by Guy Bolton and PG Wodehouse Music by George Gershwin Lyrics by Ira Gershwin
  - Ol' Man Satan: A New Musical, 1959 (Box 13, Folder 19)
    Book by Donald Heywood
  - Oliver, undated (Box 13, Folder 20)
    Book, Music and Lyrics by Lionel Bart
  - "On Getting 'Mr. Apley' Straight,"New York Times cover, November 26, 1944 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - On the Town [early working script with annotations], 1944 (Box 13, Folder 22)
    Book and Lyrics by Betty Comden and Adolph Green
  - On the Town, [1944] (Box 13, Folder 23)
    Book by Betty Comden and Adolph Green Music by Leonard Bernstein
  - On the Twentieth Century, [1978] (Box 13, Folder 24)
    Book and Lyrics by Betty Comden and Adolph Green Music by Cy Coleman
  - On Your Toes, undated (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Once Upon a Mattress, 1959 (Box 13, Folder 26)
    Book by Jay Thompson, Marshall Barer and Dean Fuller Music by Mary Rodgers Lyrics by Marshall Barer
  - One Hundred and Ten in the Shade: A Musical Play, undated (Box 13, Folder 27)
    By N. Richard Nash Music by Harvey Schmidt Lyrics by Tom Jones
  - One Mo' Time [revised], April 8, 1981 (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - One Night Stand, 1980 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    Book and Lyrics by Herb Gardner Music by Jule Styne
  - One Shining Moment: A Musical, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    by Allan Jay Friedman and Leslie Bricusse
  - Orfeu da Conceicao (Tragedia Carioca), undated (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Out of this World [final script], 1950 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    Book by Dwight Taylor and Reginald Lawrence Music and Lyrics by Cole Porter
  - Out of this World [revised], 1956 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Panama Hattie, [1940] (Box 14, Folder 6)
    Music and lyrics by Cole Porter Book by Herbert Fields and B. G. De Sylva
  - Paperback Originals: A New Musical, 1986 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    Book by Bruce Peyton Music and Lyrics by David Spencer
  - Parade: A Satirical Revue, [1935] (Box 14, Folder 8)
    Music by Jerome Morose Lyrics by Paul Peters, George Sklar and Kyle Crichton
  - Paris: A Comedy with Music in Three Acts, [1928] (Box 14, Folder 9)
    Book by Martin Brown Music by Cole Porter Lyrics by E. Ray Goetz and Cole Porter
  - Park Avenue: A Musical Comedy, [1946] (Box 14, Folder 10)
    Book by Nunnally Johnson and George S. Kaufman Music by Arthur Schwartz Lyrics by Ira Gershwin
  - The Party Girl, 1977 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    Book and Lyrics by James Ackerson Music by Daryl Curry
  - The Passionate Witch, undated (Box 14, Folder 12)
    Book by William F. Brown Music by Stanley Lebowsky Lyrics by Fred Tobias
  - Peg, [1983] (Box 14, Folder 13)
    Book and Lyrics by Peggy Lee Music by Paul Horner
  - Peg O' My Heart: A Musical Comedy [first draft], undated (Box 14, Folder 14)
    Book by Robin Miller Music and Lyrics by David Heneker
  - Peggy Ann: A New Musical Comedy by Herbert Fields, [1926] (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - The Phantom of the Opera, undated (Box 14, Folder 16)
    Book by Richard Stilgoe and Andrew Lloyd Webber Music by Andrew Lloyd Webber Lyrics by Charles Hart and Richard Stillgoe
  - Phil the Fluter: A New Musical, January 1970 (Box 14, Folder 17)
    Book by Beverley Cross and Donal Giltinan Music and Lyrics by Percy French and David Heneker
  - The Pink Jungle: A New Comedy, 1959-1960 (Box 14, Folder 18)
    Book by Leslie Stevens Music and Lyrics by Vernon Duke
  - Pippin: A Musical Comedy [production script], 1974 (Box 14, Folder 19)
    Book by Roger Hirson Music and Lyrics by Stephen Schwartz
  - Platinum: A New Musical, [1978] (Box 14, Folder 20)
    Book by Will Holt and Bruce Vilanch Music by Gary William Friedman Lyrics by Will Holt
  - La Plume de Ma Tante, [1958] (Box 14, Folder 21)
    Book by Robert Dhery Music by Gerard Calvi English Lyrics by Ross Parker
  - Poison for Two, undated (Box 14, Folder 22)
    General
    by Donald E. Westlake
  - Poland, My Poland!, June 15, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 23)
    By James Kirkwood First draft (working title)
  - Present Arms: A New Musical Comedy, [1928] (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Prettybelle [first draft], 1970 (Box 14, Folder 25)
    Book and Lyrics by Bob Merrill Music by Jule Styne
  - The Prince of Grand Street, [January 9,] 1978 (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - Princess Charming, Jack Donahue version, [1930] (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - The Producers, March 1967 (Box 14, Folder 28)
    by Mel Brooks
    This copy belonged to Herbert Hartig
  - Quasimodo [second draft], 1977 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    Book by Anthony Scully Music by Larry Grossman Lyrics by Hal Hackady
  - Quilt: A Musical Celebration, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    Book by Jim Morgan, Merle Hubbard and John Schak Music by Michael Stockler Lyrics by Jim Morgan
  - Rags, 1988 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    Book by Joseph Stein Music by Charles Strouse Lyrics by Stephen Schwartz
  - Rags: A New Musical, [1986] (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Rainbow, [1928] (Box 15, Folder 5)
    Book by Laurence Stallings and Oscar Hammerstein II Music by Vincent Youmans Lyrics by Oscar Hammerstein II
  - Red, Hot and Blue: A Musical Comedy, [1936] (Box 15, Folder 6)
    Book by Howard Lindsay and Russell [Crouse]
  - Redhead, [1959] (Box 15, Folder 7)
    Book by Herbert and Dorothy Fields and David Shaw Music by Albert Hague Lyrics by Dorothy Fields
  - Reuben Reuben: A Musical Play, 1955 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    Book and Music by Marc Blitzstein
  - Revenge with Music: in Two Acts, 1934 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    Book and Lyrics by Howard Dietz Music by Arthur Schwartz
  - Rex: A Musical, December 23, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    Book by Sherman Yellen Music by Richard Rodgers Lyrics by Sheldon Harnick
  - The Rink: A New Musical, March 10, 1983 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Riverwind: A Musical Play, 1962 (Box 15, Folder 12)
    Book, Music and Lyrics by John Jennings
  - The Roar of the Greasepaint, the Smell of the Crowd: A New Musical, June 1965 (Box 15, Folder 13)
    Book, Music and Lyrics by Leslie Bricusse and Anthony Newley
  - Roberta, [1933] (Box 15, Folder 14)
    Book and Lyrics by Otto Harbach Music by Jerome Kern
  - A Rock Carol: A New Musical, 1995 (Box 15, Folder 15)
    Book by Jim Morgan and BJ Leiderman Music by BJ Leiderman Lyrics by Jim Morgan
  - Rosalie, [1928] (Box 15, Folder 16)
    Book by William Anthony McGuire and Guy Bolton Music by Sigmund Romberg and George Gershwin Lyrics by P.G. Wodehouse and Ira Gershwin
  - Royal Flush: A Musical, [1964] (Box 15, Folder 17)
    Book by Jay Tompson and Robert Schlitt Music and Lyrics by Jay Thompson
  - Roza, 1982 (Box 15, Folder 18)
    Book and Lyrics by Julian More Music by Gilbert Becaud
  - Rumple, 1957 (Box 15, Folder 19)
    Book by Irving Phillips Music by Jack Schweikert Lyrics by Frank Reardon
  - Sadie Thompson: A Musical Play in Two Acts, [1944] (Box 15, Folder 20)
    by Howard Dietz and Vernon Duke
  - Sail Away, 1961 (Box 15, Folder 21)
    Book by Noel Coward
  - Sail Away, 1962 (Box 15, Folder 22)
    by Noel Coward
  - A Saint She Ain't: A Galaxy of Movie Greats in 1943's Swellest Screen Musical!, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 23)
    Book and Lyrics by Dick Vosburgh Music by Denis King
  - Sally, undated (Box 15, Folder 24)
    Book by Guy Bolton Music by Jerome Kern
  - Salvation: The New Rock Musical, [1969] (Box 15, Folder 25)
    by C.C. Courtney and Peter Link
  - Saratoga [first draft], 1959 (Box 15, Folder 26)
    Book by Morton Da Costa
  - Sarava, [1979] (Box 15, Folder 27)
    Book and Lyrics by N. Richard Nash Music by Mitch Leigh
  - Saturday Night: A Musical Comedy, 1954 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    Book by Julius J. Epstein and Phillip G. Epstein Music and Lyrics by Stephen Sondheim
  - Say When, [1934] (Box 16, Folder 2)
    Book by John McGowan Music by Ray Henderson Lyrics by Ted Koehler
  - The Secret Garden, February 12, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    Book and lyrics by Marsha Norman Music by Lucy Simon
  - Seesaw, 1971 (Box 72, Folder 20)
  - The Selling of the President, December 1971 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    Book by Jack O'Brien and Stuart Hample Music by Bob James Lyrics by Jack O'Brien
  - Semi Monde: A Comedy in Three Acts, undated (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Sensations, undated (Box 16, Folder 6)
    Book by Paul Zakrezewski and Wally Harper
  - Serious Fun: A Musical Revue, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    Book by Jim Morgan Music by Alan Cove, B.J. Leiderman, Bob Lindner, Da Via Sacks, Donald Siegal, Madeline Stone and Paul Trueblood
  - Seven Brides for Seven Brothers, 1978 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    Book by Larry Kasha and David Landay Music by Gene de Paul Lyrics by Johnny Mercer
  - The Seven Year Itch [new dramatists reading], undated (Box 16, Folder 9)
    Book and Lyrics by Jeffery Monday Music by Fred Werner
  - Sherry! (II): A Musical Comedy, January 30, 1967 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    Book and lyrics by James Lipton Music by Laurence Rosenthal
  - Shot Thru the Heart: A Western Musical Comedy, 1983 (Box 16, Folder 11)
    by Paul Giovanni
  - Show Boat, undated (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Show Girl, 1929 (Box 16, Folder 13)
    Book by William Anthony McGuire and JP McEnvoy Music by George Gershwin Lyrics by Ira Gershwin and Gus Kahn
  - Side by Side by Sondheim: A Musical Entertainment, 1978 (Box 16, Folder 14)
    Music and Lyrics by Stephen Sondheim and Leonard Bernstein, Mary Rodgers, Richard Rodgers and Jule Styne Continuity by Ned Sherrin
  - Side Show, [November 1, 1963] (Box 16, Folder 15)
    Book by Arthur Laurents Music and Lyrics by Stephen Sondheim
  - Silk Stockings, [1955] (Box 16, Folder 16)
    Book by George S. Kaufman, Leueen McGrath and Abe Burrows Music and Lyrics by Cole Porter
  - Simon Says: A New Musical, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 17)
    Book by Lionel Wilson and Fred Ebb Music by Paul Klein Lyrics by Fred Ebb
  - Simple Simon, [1930] (Box 16, Folder 18)
    Book by Ed Wynn and Guy Bolton Music and Lyrics by Hart and Rodgers
  - Sing Out the News, [1938] (Box 16, Folder 19)
    Music and Lyrics by Harold J. Rome
  - Singin' in the Rain [revised rehearsal draft], 1986 (Box 16, Folder 20)
    Book by Betty Comden and Adolph Green Music and Lyrics by Nacio Herb Brown and Arthur Freed
  - Singin' the Blues, [1931] (Box 16, Folder 21)
    Book by John McGowan Music by James McHugh Lyrics by Dorothy Fields
  - Sitting Pretty: A Musical Comedy, [1924] (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Smile, 1983 (Box 72, Folder 21)
  - Smiles, November 18, 1930 (Box 16, Folder 26)
    Book by William Anthony McGuire Music by Vincent Youmans Lyrics by Harold Adamson, Clifford Grey and Ring Lardner
  - Snoopy!!! [revised], December 10, 1982 (Box 16, Folder 27)
    Book by Warren Lockhart, Arthur Whitelaw, and Michael L. Grace Music by Larry Grossman Lyrics by Hal Hackady
  - Something for the Boys, 1943 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Something More! [revised], July 15, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    Book by Nate Monaster Music by Sammy Fain Lyrics by Marilyn and Alan Bergman
  - Sometime: A Musical Play in 2 Acts, [1918] (Box 17, Folder 3)
    Book and Lyrics by Rida Johnson Young
  - A Song for Anastasia: A Musical Play, [1965] (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - The Song of the Flame, undated (Box 17, Folder 5)
    Book by Otto Harbach and Oscar Hammerstein 2nd Music by George Gershwin and Herbert Stothart
  - Soon, [1971] (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Sophie: A Musical Play Based on the Life of Sophie Tucker, [1963] (Box 17, Folder 7)
    Book by Phillip Pruneau Music and Lyrics by Steve Allen
  - Sophisticated Ladies, 1981 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Spinoff, undated (Box 17, Folder 9)
    David Rabe
  - Spokesong, or the Common Wheel, [1979] (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Spotlight, undated (Box 17, Folder 11)
    Book by Richard Seff Music by Jerry Bresler Lyrics by Lyn Duddy
  - Spring is Here: A Musical Comedy [corrected version], 1929 (Box 17, Folder 12)
    Book by Owen Davis Music by Richard Rodgers Lyrics by Lorenz Hart
  - Stars in Your Eyes: A Musical Comedy, [1939] (Box 17, Folder 13)
    Book by JP McEnvoy Music by Arthur Schwartz Lyrics by Dorothy Fields
  - Starting Here, Starting Now, undated (Box 17, Folder 14)
    Music by David Shire Lyrics by Richard Maltby, Jr.
  - State Fair [rehearsal script], 1995 (Box 17, Folder 15)
    Book by Tom Briggs and Louis Mattioli Music by Richard Rodgers Lyrics by Oscar Hammerstein II
  - Stop! Look! Listen!, [1915] (Box 17, Folder 16)
    Book by [Harry] B. Smith Music by Jerome [Kean]
  - Stop the World – I Want to Get Off, [1962] (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Street Scene [final pre-rehearsal version], 1946 (Box 17, Folder 18)
    Book by Elmer Rice Music by Kurt Weill Lyrics by Langston Hughes
  - Strike up the Band, [1927] (Box 17, Folder 19)
    Book by George S. Kaufman Music by George Gershwin Lyrics by Ira Gershwin
  - Strike Up the Band!, 1984 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Subways are for Sleeping, December 27, 1961 (Box 17, Folder 21)
    Book and Lyrics by Betty Comden and Adolph Green Music by Jule Styne
  - Sugar: A New Musical Comedy, [1972] (Box 17, Folder 22)
    Book by Peter Stone Music by Jule Styne Lyrics by Bob Merrill
  - Sugar: A New Musical Comedy [LA version], 1977 (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - Suits Me Fine, undated (Box 17, Folder 24)
    Book by Preston Sturges Music and Lyrics by Hugh Martin
  - Sunday in the Park with George [May 31, 1983 version] (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - Sunday in the Park with George [February 13, 1984 version] (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - Sunny River, [1941] (Box 17, Folder 27)
    Books and Lyrics by Oscar Hammerstein, 2nd Music by Sigmund Romberg
  - Sunset Boulevard: The Musical, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 28)
    Book and Lyrics by Don Black and Christopher Hampton Music by Andrew Lloyd Webber
  - Sweet Adeline, [1929] (Box 18, Folder 1)
    by Oscar Hammerstein II and [Jerome Kern]
  - Sweet Little Devil: A Musical Comedy in Three Acts, [1924] (Box 18, Folder 2)
    By Lawrence Schwab and Frank Kandel
  - Sweet Mianie, [Sheila] Smith copy, undated (Box 18, Folder 3)
    Book by Stuart Bishop Music and Lyrics by Ed Tyler
  - Sweet Mistress [original mimeo], December 6, 1961 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    Book by Ira Wallach Music by Don Walker Lyrics by Ira Wallach and Don Walker
  - Swing: A Musical Romance [rehearsal version], 1980 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    Book by Conn Fleming Music by Robert Waldman Lyrics by Alfred Uhry
  - Take Me Along, undated (Box 18, Folder 6)
    Booky by Joseph Stein and Robert Russell Music and Lyrics by Bob Merrill
  - Tangerine: An Original Musical Comedy in Two Acts, [1921] (Box 18, Folder 7)
    Book by Guy Bolton Music by Carlo Sanders Lyrics by Howard Johnson
  - Tattered Tom: A New Musical, undated (Box 18, Folder 8)
    Book by Timothy Gray Songs by Hugh Martin and Ralph Blane
  - Tell Me More!: A Musical Comedy in Two Acts, 1925 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    Book by Fred Thompson and William K. Wells Music by George Gershwin Lyrics by Ira Gershwin and BG DeSylva
  - That's the Ticket, undated (Box 18, Folder 10)
    Book by J.J. Epstein and P.G. Epstein Music and Lyrics by Harold Rome
  - There Must be a Pony!, undated (Box 18, Folder 11)
    by James Kirkwood
  - They're Playing Our Song, 1979 (Box 72, Folder 23)
  - Three's a Crowd!, undated (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Three Wishes for Jamie [final revised copy by Arthur Norris], [1952] (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Through the Years, [1932] (Box 18, Folder 14)
    Book by Brian Hooker Music by Vincent Youmans Lyrics by Edward Heyman
    contain marginalia
  - Timbuktu!, 1977 (Box 72, Folder 24)
  - A Time for Singing, 1965 (Box 18, Folder 15)
    Book and Lyrics by Gerald Freedman and John Morris Music by John Morris
  - "A Time for Singing" Review, Newspaper clipping, [1966] (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - The Times: A New Musical [revised incomplete draft], November 1991 (Box 18, Folder 17)
    Book and Lyrics by Joe Keenan Music by Brad Ross
    Revised incomplete draft performed at Manhattan Theatre Club, November 1991
  - Tip-Toes, undated (Box 72, Folder 25)
  - Too Many Girls, [1939] (Box 18, Folder 18)
    Book by George Marion, Jr. Music by Richard Rogers Lyrics by Lorenz Hart
  - Toujours Forever, undated (Box 18, Folder 19)
    Book by Don Ettlinger Music by Harold [ome]
  - Tovarich: A Musical Comedy, [1963] (Box 18, Folder 20)
    Book by David Shaw Lyrics by Anne Croswell Music by Lee Pockriss
  - Treasure Girl [corrected to December 17th, 1928] (Box 18, Folder 21)
    Book by Fred Thompson and Vincent Lawrence Music by George Gershwin Lyrics by Ira Gershwin
  - Two by Two: A Musical Comedy [Final production script], November 10, 1970 (Box 18, Folder 22)
    Book by Peter Stone Music by Richard Rogers Lyrics by Martin Charnin
    Final production script
  - Two on the Aisle, [1951] (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - Two's Company [final], [1952] (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - The Umbrellas of Cherbourg [version A, performance script], February 1, 1978 (Box 18, Folder 25)
    Book by Jacques Demy Music by Michel Legrand
  - Underworld: A Musical Play, undated (Box 18, Folder 26)
    Book by Ben Hecht and Ted Yates Lyrics by John Hollander and Lester Judson Music by Jerome Moross
  - Up in Central Park, 1970 (Box 18, Folder 27)
    Music by Sigmund Romberg Lyrics by Dorothy Fields Book by Herbert and Dorothy Fields
  - Urban Cowboy, 2002 (Box 18, Folder 28)
    Book by Phillip Oesterman and Aaron Latham
  - The Vagabond King, [1925] (Box 18, Folder 29)
    Music by Rudolf Friml Book and lyrics by Russell Janey and Brian Hooker Additional dialogue by W. H. Post
  - Very Good Eddie, [1915] (Box 19, Folder 1)
    Book by Philip Bartholomae and Guy Bolton Music by Jerome Kern Lyrics by Schuyler Greene
  - Very Warm for May: A Musical Play, [1939] (Box 19, Folder 2)
    Book and Lyrics by Oscar Hammerstein 2nd. Music by Jerome Kern
  - Victor/Victoria, [1995] (Box 19, Folder 3)
    Book by Blake Edwards Music by Henry Mancini Lyrics by Leslie Briusse
  - Victory Canteen, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    Music and lyrics by the Sherman Brothers Book by Larsen and Lauher
  - Virginia, 1937 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    Book by Laurence Stillman and Owen Davis Music by Arthur Schwartz Lyrics by Albert Stillman
  - Watch Your Step, [1914] (Box 19, Folder 6)
    By Harry B. Smith Music by Irving Berlin
  - W.C., 1971 (Box 72, Folder 26)
  - Welcome, Darlings, undated (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - What a Day for a Miracle: A Tale of a Children's Crusade, undated (Box 19, Folder 8)
    Book by Henry Myers and E.Y. Harburg Music by Larry Orenstein and Jeff Alexander Lyrics by E.Y. Harburg
  - What's with Emily?: A Homicidal Musical, undated (Box 19, Folder 9)
    Book and lyrics by Rory Bruce Denis and Larry Becker Music by Donald Oliver
  - Whoppee, undated (Box 19, Folder 10)
    Includes property plots, electrical plots, and wardrobe
  - Whoop-Up: A New Musical Comedy, [1958] (Box 19, Folder 11)
    Book by Cy Feuer, Ernest H. Martin and Dan Cushman Music by Moose Charlap Lyrics by Norman Gimbel
  - Who's Who 1938 [incomplete script] (Box 19, Folder 12)
    incomplete script
  - Wildcat, 1960 (Box 19, Folder 13)
    Book by N. Richard Nash Music by Cy Coleman Lyrics by Carolyn Leigh
  - Windy City: A New Musical, undated (Box 19, Folder 14)
    Music by Tony Macaulay Book and Lyrics by Dick Vosburgh
  - Wish You Were Here: A Musical Play, [1952] (Box 19, Folder 15)
    Book by Arthur Kober and Joshua Logan Music and Lyrics by Harold Rome
  - The Wizard of Oz, 1930 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Woman of the Year: A Musical Comedy [rehearsal script], December 29, 1980 (Box 19, Folder 17)
    Book by Peter Stone Music and Lyrics by John Kander and Fred Ebb
    Rehearsal script
  - Working: A Musical, 1978 (Box 19, Folder 18)
    Book by Stephen Schwartz and Nina Faso Songs by Craig Carnelia, Micki Grant, Mary Rodgers, Susan Birkenhead, Stephen Schwartz and James Taylor
  - You Never Know, [1938] (Box 19, Folder 19)
    By Cole Porter
  - [Ziegfeld] Follies of 1907: A Review of the Year (Box 19, Folder 20)
    By Harry B. Smith
  - [Ziegfeld] Follies of 1907: A Review of the Year (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - [Ziegfeld] Follies of 1908 (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - [Ziegfeld] Follies of 1908 (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - Ziegfeld Follies of 1909 (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - Ziegfeld Follies of 1934 (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - Ziegfeld Follies of 1934 (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - Ziegfeld Follies of 1936 (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - Ziegfeld Follies of 1936 (Box 19, Folder 28)
  - Zorba, undated (Box 19, Folder 29)
    Book by Joseph Stein Music by John Kander Lyrics by Fred Ebb
- Series II: Screenplays and Teleplays
  This series comprises screenplays and teleplays for films and television productions. The documents range from final edited versions of scripts to working first and second drafts. Notable productions include Titanic, On a Clear Day You Can See Forever, and Evita.
  - A Chorus Line, July 26, 1984 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    Screenplay by Arnold Schulman
  - Boogie Nights [draft], September 1995 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Cole Porter's Les Girls, 1957 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    Screenplay by John Patrick Music and Lyrics by Cole Porter Starring Gene Kelly, Mitzi Gaynor, and Kay Kendall
  - Dynasty: Episode 102 (16), "Foreign Relations" [first draft], November 6, 1984 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    Teleplay by Edward DeBlasio
  - East Side/West Side: A Screenplay [first draft], undated (Box 20, Folder 5)
    By James Kirkwood and Gerald S. Paonessa
  - Everything You Always Wanted to Know About Sex* (*But Were Afraid to Ask), [1972] (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Evita [Second draft screenplay, revised], June 10, 1982 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    Screenplay by Ken Russell Music by Andrew Lloyd Webber Lyrics by Tim Rice
  - Gigi: A Musical Film Play, [1958] (Box 20, Folder 8)
    Screenplay and lyrics by Alan Jay Lerner Music by Frederick Loewe
  - Jumbo, September 6, 1962 (Box 20, Folder 10)
    Screenplay by Sidney Sheldon Directed by Charles Waters Starring Doris Day, Stephen Boyd, Jimmy Durante, Martha Raye
  - Little Me, undated (Box 20, Folder 11)
    By Larry Gelbart
    First draft screenplay
  - The Messiah on Mott Street: A Christmas Musical for Television [third draft, two-hour version], August 3, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 12)
    Teleplay and Lyrics by David Spencer Music by Alan Manken
  - Moonlight and Love Songs, 1984 (Box 20, Folder 13)
    Screenplay by Marc Alan Zagoren Directed by Peter Bennett
  - On a Clear Day You Can See Forever, June 16, 1970 (Box 20, Folder 14)
    Screenplay and lyrics by Alan Jay Lerner Music by Burton Lane Directed by Vincente Minnelli Starring Barbara Streisand
  - The Opposite of Sex: An Original Screenplay, undated (Box 20, Folder 15)
    Screenplay by Don Roos
  - The Phil Silvers Show: The Ballad of Louie the Louse, October 16, 1959 (Box 20, Folder 17)
    Teleplay by Nat Hiken Starring: Phil Silvers, Eddie Albert, Betsy Palmer, and Pert Kelton
  - Time of Reckoning: A Screenplay, July 23, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 18)
    Screenplay by David Spencer
  - Titanic: A Screenplay, May 7, 1996 (Box 20, Folder 19)
    Screenplay by James Cameron
  - To Wong Foo, Thanks for Everything, Julie Newmar [first draft], November 5, 1993 (Box 20, Folder 20)
    Screenplay by Douglas Carter Beane
  - A Walk in the Clouds [revised first draft], [1995] (Box 20, Folder 21)
    By Robert Mark Kamen
  - What's Up Doc? [revised final screenplay], August 1, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 22)
    Screenplay by Buck Henry From original story by David Newman, Robert Benton, Peter Bogdanovich
    Final revised script
- Series III: Conductor Scores and Orchestrations